I do not think institutions are here in size at all.
When I think of institution, I think of the large pension
plans, the large endowments, insurance companies,
sovereign wealth funds.
And some of those flows have started for sure.
So the type of institution that I have spent my career with
mostly have still--
they haven't even scratched the surface.
Were you?
Oh, not at all, not at all.
Welcome to Bankless, where we explore the frontier of
internet money and internet finance.
This is Ryan Sean Adams.
Just me here today, David is out.
So I am here to help you become more bankless.
We've got Eric Peters on the podcast today.
This is our third time talking.
I consider Eric an absolute investing legend.